and I'm
y
really going to rule this out
real esto lo voy a descartar
Okay, two more little things and we're going to get into a
Eh vale dos cosillas más y nos vamos a
real fight, okay, today we have
liar con moño vale que hoy tenemos aquí
the biggest thing here that we have to discuss,
lo más grande que tenemos que comentar
okay, On the one
vale Por una
hand, On the other hand, yes, I wanted to
parte Por una parte sí que quería
comment on this, okay, today we discussed it
comentar Esto vale hoy lo hemos tratado
on the afternoon news, okay, and it
en el noticiero de por la tarde vale Y
's
es
[Music]
[Música]
that today is today, not today, Barbara Rey sits down,
que hoy es hoy no hoy se sienta Bárbara
no today, no, today is
no hoy que no hoy es
Tuesday, in other words, Barbara Rey sits down on
martes o sea Bárbara Rey se sienta el
Monday, no because it was a Monday, of
lunes no porque era un lunes de
course, Monday, it's next Monday. I'm I
lunes claro es el lunes que viene estoy
'm really, it seems like I'm smoking
estoy de verdad parece que me fumo el
Pepa's ass, eh. I mean, I don't even understand
poto de la [__] eh O sea no me entero ni
on the day that I'm living, it's
en el día que vivo sea el claro de lunes
called Monday, of course, that means it's next Monday, of course.
se llama eso significa que es el lunes
Okay,
que viene claro Vale
and we're clear, we're clear. No, what's
y Y tenemos claro tenemos claro No qué
going on, u
pasa u
Russell, russ
Russell russ
Russell,
Russell u
u Russell. Oh, Russell, we're clear. Of course, that
Russell Uy russel tenemos Claro que que
if Barbara Rey goes on the
si lunes va Bárbara Rey al programa de
Friday program on Monday, we're not absolutely clear
viernes de lunes no tenemos clarísimo
that on Friday the son is going, no, to answer,
que el viernes va el hijo no a contestar
no, and to comment on it, no, we assume that, I do
no y a comentarlo no eso lo asumimos
n't disappear for a long
no desaparezco durante una larga
time, but bun bun and bun a  I kiss
temporada pero moño moño y moñe un beso
my captain the sad one Oh that's my
mi capitana la triste Oh que es mi
Mercedes Mercedes how about time how are you
Mercedes Mercedes que de tiempo cómo
Tell me something in the chat How are you No don't
estás Dime algo en el chat Cómo está No
spend money on a Super chat
no te gastes dinero en un Super chat
But tell me Tell me Hey better or what's going on No
Pero dímelo Dime Oye mejor o qué pasa No
if it's true that it's true daughter that we missed you my goodness
si es verdad que es verdad hija que te
Russell my goodness Russell
russel madre mía rassel en
seriously listen to me do you remember That Ángel
serio escúchame os acordáis Que Ángel
Garó when he came he was telling us
garó cuando vino nos estuvo comentando
that they called him for
que lo llamaron para
a Big Brother Duo Where is that Where is that
un gran hermano Dúo Dónde está eso
here look how good this live was eh
aquí mira qué bueno fue este directo eh
how great this live was
qué buenísimo fue este directo
eh look look Listen to
eh
this because reality
mira mira Escuchar esto porque reality
has said no now they've also offered me to go to I don't
ha dicho que no ahora me han ofrecido ir
know what Duo there is I said
también a no sé qué Dúo hay he dicho que
no to a big Hero Vancer So of
no a un gran Hero vancer Entonces por
course not but it was
supuesto que no pero era
necessary with
necesario con
quier because I'm not going to go with No but if they
quier porque no voy a ir con No pero si
've called you it's to offer you with
te han llamado es para ofrecerte con
someone who was that
alguien quién era el
someone no no they haven't told me who I
alguien no no me han dicho con quien yo
would like to be with is that realize Big Brother
quisiera es que date cuenta gran hermano
that you remember me you do
que me os acordáis
n't remember
no os acordáis
No well Look at what Kiko says now it's
No pues Mirad lo que dice Kiko ahora es
more the interview with Bárbara Rey is
más la entrevista de Bárbara Rey es el
next Monday December 9th who will
próximo lunes día 9 de diciembre quién
sit on the
se sienta el día
13th Oh thank you Carmen darling I can almost not
13 Ay gracias Carmen corazón que casi no
hear you queen Carmen Asenjo
te escucho reina Carmen asenjo Muchas
Thank you very much Thank you
gracias muchísimas
very much Thank you very much Yes yes it is my
Gracias Muchísimas gracias Sí sí es mi
saint's day we have already talked about it before in fact
Santo ya lo hemos hablado antes es más
Barbara Rey's interview is
la entrevista de Bárbara Rey es el
next Monday December 9th who will
próximo lunes día 9 de diciembre quién
sit on the 13th December on
se sienta el día 13 de diciembre en de
Friday to answer her mother of course
viernes para contestar a su madre claro
her son Angel Cristo Junior Of course they
su hijo Ángel Cristo Junior Claro ya lo
have everything planned it's going to be a
tienen todo planificado van a ser unas
beautiful Christmas but who have they
navidades preciosas pero en quién han
thought of for the next debate for
pensado para para el próximo debate para
the next reality show which is why we were saying
el próximo reality que por eso decíamos
that it's going to be very expensive man the
que te va a salir muy caro hombre el
next debate that has stockings is called
próximo debate que tiene medias se llama
GH reality Sorry reality the next
gh reality Perdón reality el próximo
reality show on Tele5 is called GH Duo
reality que tiene tele5 se llama gh Dúo
well then they will see each other face to face then
bien pues ahí se verán las caras luego
don't look so surprised when they
no os pongáis caraa de sorpresa cuando
tell you open the door to see who's
os digan abre la puerta a ver quién hay
in the next debate in the next
en el próximo debate en el próximo
reality show sorry I have a fever and the
reality perdon que estoy con fiebre y
flu in the next reality show that
con gripe en el próximo reality que
Tele5 premieres in January I can't believe it they will
estrena tele5 en enero no me lo creo se
see each other face to face
ven las caras Bárbara Rey Sofía Cristo y
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Christ, watch out. Because Kiko jumped into the
Cristo ojo Porque aquí se ha tirado a la
pool here. I understand that to jump into
piscina Kiko entiendo que para tirarse a
the pool here he has to have this
la piscina aquí tiene que tener esto
too tied up.
demasiado atado
No, I mean, if it turns out this is a
no o sea esto como se cumpla es una
huge, huge bomb.
pedazo pedasí sima de bomba
Let's see, Silvia, if it turns out this is a huge, huge bomb. It
eh A ver Silvia esto como se cumpla es
's no
una pedazo pedasí simo de bomba no es
small thing. It's
poca cosa
no small
eh No es poca
thing, a circus. Let's
cosa un circo a
see who would you all say is the worst
ver quién diríais ustedes que queda peor
of the three, if you lend yourself to
de los tres si se prestan a
that. Opinions quickly, okay, we have
eso opiniones rápido vale que tenemos
to move on to the next topic. Who would you all say is the
que pasar siguiente tema quién diríais
worst if
ustedes que queda Peor si se presta
that happens? Bichi, you're making me blush.
eso bichi me estás poniendo Colorado eh
Hey, eh, come on here. One was a priro,
Oye eh pasa aquí uno era un priro
carando. Two, pun, Moño lover. Three, I
carando dos pun amante del Moño tres te
always see you, but ind delayed while I
veo siempre pero ind diferido mientras
clean, that's why he didn't donate. Four godfather. Oh,
limpio por eso no donó cuatro padrino Uy
that's left in the air, eh Bichi. Let's see, I don't
quedó eso en el aire eh bichi A ver no
know, I haven't thought about it. eh, I haven't thought about it. No, I don't know,
sé no lo he pensado eh No lo he pensado
the truth is, I haven't thought about it. The
no no sé la verdad no lo he pensado La
truth is, it seems a
verdad se me hace un
little, I don't know, strange, I don't know, I think it's okay,
poco no sé raro no sé lo pienso vale
for me. The three of them. How shameless,
em para mí Los tres Qué poca vergüenza
of course, it's the three of them, but on one hand, of course,
claro es que los tres pero por una parte
the
la
mother, I mean, I think  that the mother would look worse
madre o sea yo creo que quedaría peor la
because she's the one who's been
madre no porque es a la que han
beaten up
vapuleado
no I mean the son in the end is the one who has
no O sea el hijo al final es el que ha
given it his all in the end son would get a great
dado caña al final hijo le saldría
deal But they don't have to for me
redondo el negocio Pero no a m a tienen
Mari Carmen Thank you very much sweetheart you
que Mari Carmen Muchas gracias corazón
could have written something eh Beautiful more
podías haber escrito algo eh Guapa más
How
Que
beautiful that between that between the emeritus
guapa que entre que entre el emérito
also no that he's accused now they didn't
también no que está imputado ahora no
say the other day in a
dijeron el otro día en una
news story let's see I think that the one who would lower herself the most there
noticia a ver yo creo que la que más se
would be the mother [ __ ] It's that
rebajaría ahí sería la madre hostias Es
look at you not a person what
que fíjate tú no persona lo que ha sido
Bárbara Rey has been to get into a Big Brother
Bárbara Rey meterse en un gran hermano
Duo And on top of that in those conditions
Dúo Y encima en esas condiciones después
after being trampled the son would get a
de ser pisoteada el hijo le saldría
great deal of business of course the son of a [ __ ]
redondo el negocio claro el hijo de [__]
mother but then also
madre pero luego además
the daughter Well but they don't have to for me
el la hija Bueno pero no a m ae tienen
all of it is for a good bun and many
que todos sea por un buen moño y muchos
fascinating kisses kiss red heart can I can't
fasc lando bes beso corazón rojo pued no
believe that you are so addicted to
me puedo creer que sois tan adictos al
gossip that we are going to reach the challenge of 30
chisme que vamos a llegar al reto de 30
super chat but I mean by face
super chat pero o sea by the face
eh Because look Because yes because you really
eh Porque mira Porque sí porque os
want the bun No I
apetece mucho el moño No yo
sincerely no  I am very convinced, eh,
sinceramente no estoy muy convencido eh
I am not very convinced that we
yo no estoy muy convencido de que
should continue being
de que debamos continuar siendo un canal
such an aggressive and dirty channel.
tan agresivo y tan sucio